Blondell Hill Gospel Music Collection, circa 1916-1964 SC 158
Archives of African American Music and Culture
Blondell Hill Gospel Music Collection
1916-1964
1940-1964
Archives of African American Music and Culture
Hill, Blondell, 1904-2005
SC 158
1 document case 0.21 linear feet
This collection consists of gospel song books and sheet music, song texts, photographs, and other ephemeral material related to Blondell Hill's participation with choirs in Richmond, Indiana, Petoskey, Michigan, and Harbor Springs, Michigan.
Arrangement
Arranged in two series:
Series 1: Gospel Music
Series 2: Ephemera
Biographical / Historical
Blondell Harris Hill was born in Marianna, Arkansas on February 9, 1904. At the age of 19 she was recruited to attend Earlham College and moved to Richmond, Indiana. At Earlham she completed two years of study, including music, piano, and other required course work. She then married Roy Hill, whose mother owned the Mary E. Hill Nursing Home in Richmond, Indiana. Blondell Hill was active as a church musician and played for the Sunday School and the Senior Choir at the Bethel A.M.E. church in Richmond. She passed her love of music on to her daughter, Rochelle, who sang in the children's and junior choirs.
Hill also worked for the Leeds family in Richmond as a cook. They spent the summers of 1952-1956 in the resort town of Petoskey, Michigan, where Hill performed with a local gospel choir. Originally formed by a seasonal household employee from Dayton, Ohio, the choir was comprised of African Americans in the Petoskey area who came from Michigan, Indiana, Wisconsin, and Kentucky to work in the resort town. Since there was no African American church in Petoskey and most of the household employees had been accustomed to singing in gospel choirs, the employers in the area made sure their help became familiar with the other Black household employees and directed them to a church that was preferred by the seasonal workers. Hill and her daughter both performed in the Petoskey Gospel Volunteer Choir and are pictured in the photograph included in the collection.
Blondell Hill passed away at the age of 101 on August 26, 2005, and is buried in Earlham Cemetery, Richmond, Indiana. Rochelle Hill Tinsley attended Indiana University, graduating with a BS in 1976 and an MS in 1978.
Access Restrictions
Use of time-based media materials (audio and video) may require production of listening or viewing copies.
Access to streaming audio, moving image, and full resolution digital image materials may currently be restricted to researchers who can authenticate with an IU account or who are physically present on campus. Remote streaming to individual researchers may be allowed with the completion of applicable forms.
For further information about access to online audiovisual materials, contact AAAMC staff at aaamc@indiana.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by daughter Rochelle Hill Tinsley in October 2011.
Scope and Contents
The bulk of the collection consists of gospel songbooks, sheet music, and song texts collected by Hill for use with choirs in Richmond, Indiana and Petoskey, Michigan. Songbooks and sheet music are arranged alphabetically by title. Programs, ephemera, and photographs pertain primarily to the Gospel Volunteers Choir and Harbor Springs, Michigan.
African American Church Musicians; African Americans--Michigan; gospel music; Gospel music--Indiana; Gospel music--Michigan--Petoskey; Gospel musicians; Household employees; Sheet Music; Spirituals (Songs); Dorsey, Thomas Andrew; Bowles, Lillian M.; Brewster, W. Herbert (William Herbert), 1897-1987; Campbell, Lucie Eddie, 1885-1963; Davis, E. Clifford (Eddie Clifford); Frye, Theodore R., 1899-1963; Martin, Roberta (Vocalist); Morris, Kenneth, 1917-1988; National Baptist Convention of the United States of America
- 1. Gospel Music, 1916-1964; 12 Folders
  - Bowle's Favorite Frye's Special Gospel Song Book, No. 6, 1940; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Contents:
    There's a Great Change in Me / Theo. R. Frye; Arranged by K. Morris
    I'm Waiting for Jesus, He's Waiting for Me / Thomsas A. Dorsey
    He is My Savior (And I Love Him So) / Kenneth Morris
    I'm Overshadowed By His Love / Kenneth Morris
    Jesus Love Just Bubbles Over In My Heart; Arranged by Roberta Martin and Theo. R. Frye
    Is Your All on the Altar; Arranged by Frye and Martin
    Shall I Meet You Over Yonder / Roberta Martin and Johnie E. Rogers, Jr.; Arranged by Morris
    When The Pearly Gates Unfold / A. L. Kendricks; Arranged by L. Morris
    Run and Help Us Tell / Evangelist Timpie Stancel Goldsberry; Arranged by Elma Simpson
    Didn't It Rain / Roberta Martin; Arranged by W.M. Webb
    Search My Heart / Roberta Martin and John E. Rogers Jr.
    Until I Found The Lord / Elder Brooks Jr.; Arranged by K. Morris
    I Know the Lord Has Laid His Hands on Me / Kenneth Morris; Selection, Lillian M. Bowles
    Talk About A Chile That Do Love Jesus; Arranged by Roberta martin and Theo. R. Frye
    God Will Brings Things Out All Right / W.P. Anderson; Arranged by Morris
    Walking With Jesus / N.G. Henderson
    What A Friend We Have In Jesus; Arranged by Willie Mae Ford Smith
    (I'm going to keep on praying 'till I find Him) There's a King of Kings Somewhere; Arranged by Roberta Martin and Theo. R. Frye
    I'm Not Uneasy / Rev. B.H. Hogan; Arranged by Laura B. Davis
    This Little Light of Mine; Revised, Lillian M. Bowles; Arranged by Pace
    This Precious Salvation / Rev. B.H.Hogan; Arranged by Laura B. Davis
    Try Jesus, For I know He will Answer Prayers / N.G. Henderson and L.M Bowles
    I Tell King Jesus / W.O. Hoyle; Arranged by W.O.Hoyle
    Lead Me There, My Lord, Lead Me There / J. Rufus Liddell; Arranged by J. Rufus Liddell
    Traveling to a Better Land / Rev. L.A. Pinkston; Arranged by Rev. M.C. Durham, K. Morris, L.M. Bowles
    Publisher
    Chicago, IL: Bowles Music House
  - Bowle's Favorite Gospel Songs of Joy, No. 8, 1941; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 2)
    No More Good Bye / E. Clifford Davis.
    I Know the Lord Will Make a Way / Eugene Smith
    Jesus Has Made the Way for Me / Rev. E. L. Harvell
    Your Mother Loves Her Children All the Time / Rev. E.L. Harvell
    My Father Watches Over Me / Chas. H. Gabriel
    It is Morning in My Heart / Rev. A.H. Ackley
    Hear Our Prayer / John G. Hunter
    Come On Sinner and Seek the Lord / Virginia Davis
    I've Changed My Way (Of Living Here) / Albert F. [Brumley]; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
    Let Jesus Lead You All the Way; Arranged by N.G. Henderson
    I Didn't Know Then But I Know Now / Bruton Sims; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
    There Is Something That Makes Me Know I'm His Child / Rev. A.H. Pointer; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle and L.M Bowles
    I Want to Do Something For the Lord / Virginia Davis
    Never More Will I Pass This Way / Cordelia Monroe; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
    The Lord Has Made Me Free / Kenneth Morris
    Cheer the Weary Traveler / Anon.; Arranged by Bowles and Hoyle
    I'll Do All I Can For the Lord / Rev. A. H. Pointer; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle and L.M Bowles
    Look Upon the Field / Edna L. Jones; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
    He Is the Same / Myrtle Jackson; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
    God of Our Fathers / George W. Warren; Arranged by Daniel C. Roberts
    I Know the Lord Will Hear and Answer Prayer / Essie Plunkett; Arranged by W.O.Hoyle
    So Glad I Know That He Is Mine / Kenneth Morris
    I'll See Him Some Day / J.G. Hunter; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
  - Bowles Favorite Gospel & Spiritual Songs, No. 2, 1939; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 3)
    I'll Do Anything for My Jesus / Kenneth Morris
    Jesus is the Light, Bless His Holy Name / L.M. Bowles and W.P. Anderson; Arranged by K. Morris
    Don't Take Everybody to Be Your Friend / W.P. Anderson and Lillian M. Bowles; Arranged by K. Morris
    I Am Sending My Timber Up to Heaven / Theo. R. Frye; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Have You Any Time For Jesus; Arranged by K.Morris
    Yes I Know I'm in His Care / Kenneth Morris
    Seeking for Me; Arranged by Willie Webb
    Seek and You Shall Find / Lillian M. Bowles; Arranged by K. Morris
    I'd Give Up All My Sins and Serve the Lord / L.M. Bowles and N.G. Henderson
    Somebody Touched Me / Lillian Bowles and Theo. Frye; Arranged by K. Morris
    I'm Singing for Jesus is Mine / Rev. M.C. Durham; Arranged by K. Morris
    Are You Ready (For The Coming Of The Lord) / Kenneth Morris
    On Jordan's Stormy Banks I Stand (My Mother's Song) / Roberta Martin
    Now I'm So Glad I Got Good Religion / N.G. Henderson; Arranged by K. Morris and L.M. Bowles
    Yes, I Want to See My Savior - Don't You? / Kenneth Morris
    He Calmed The Ocean / K. Morris and L.S. Boswell
    Oh! Sit Down, No I Can't Sit Down / Andrew Welch and Theo. R. Frye; Arranged by K. Morris and Andrew Welch
    He's My Rock, My Sword, My Shield / Famous 5 Soul Stirrers; Arranged by Kenneth S. Morris
    I'm on the Field / Theo. Frye and Lillian Bowles; Arranged by K. Morris
    My Mind's Made Up and My Heart is Fixed / Lillian Bowles and Willie May ford Smith; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Stand Steady, Bretheren / Andrew Welch, L.M. Bowles and Theo. R. Frye; Arranged by Morris
    You've Got to Pray to Be Ready When He Comes / Joseph C. Lands and Lillian Bowles; Arranged by K. Morris
    Working on the Building / W.O. Hoyle and Lillian M. Bowles
  - Frye's Echoes of the Baptist Music Convention, No. 1, 1948; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 4)
    I Will Move On Up A Little Higher; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    The Mercy Gate / Clarence E. Hatcher; Arranged by Bobby Hopkins
    Back To The Dust / Elvie E. Skinner; Arranged by C.C. Skinner
    Sow Righteous Seed / Rev. A.A. Childs and Robert Anderson; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    My Redeemer / Samuel A. Lewish; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    Only A Look At Jesus / Anna E. Shepherd
    Nothing can change me (Since I've Found The Lord) / H.J. Ford; Arranged by Martin
    Don't Forget The Family Prayer / Anne C. Graham
    Jesus Is The Answer He's All I Need / Willie Webb
    Thy Holy Will Be Done / Charles Banks
    I'm Going To Rest From My Labor Afterwhile / Rev. Nathaniel Betts; Arranged by Aletha M. Robinson
    Yes, Yes, Yes, I Love Jesus / Samuel E. Lewis; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    My Lord Has Need Of Me / Emma L. Jackson
    Oh Be Ready For The Coming Of The Lord / Emma. L. Jackson and Elizabeth Barken
    I Just Can't Serve The Lord As I Desire / Rev. Nathaniel Betts; Arranged by Aletha M. Robinson
    Lord, I Can't Stay On This Highway By Myself / Virginia Davis
    Somebody Saved Me / H.J. Ford
    Onward, Christian Soldiers / Arthur Sullivan and Sabine Baring-Gould
    Jesus / Mary Lou Coleman; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    Bye and Bye I Will See Jesus / I. J. Johnson; Arranged by Margery and Freddie J.E. Harris
    In The Upper Room With Jesus / Lucie E. Campbell
    Where Jesus Leads Me (I Will Follow) / Myrtle Jackson; Arranged by Jeanette Tall
    Let Us Sing Till The Pow'r Of The Lord Come Down / A.B. Windom
    Yield Not To Temptation / H.R. Palmer
    Even Me / Conder; Arranged by Morris
    It's Cool Down Here By The Banks of Jordan / Emma L. Jackson; Arranged by Virigina Davis
    The Great and Last Convention / Elvie Skinner; Arranged by C.C. Skinner
    I Have Made A Promise And I Can't Turn Around / W.L. Farmer; Arranged by Odessa Steward
    Tired / John Walter Davis; Arranged by E. Cliffored Davis
    He Is Able / H.J. Ford
    Were You There / Anon.
    Why Should I Worry? / Robert Anderson; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    Speak To Me Jesus / Rev. W. Herbert Brewster D.D.; Arranged by W.O. Hoyle
    Down On My Knees / H.J. Ford
    Tell It, Sing It, Shout It / James D. Walbert and James Rowe
    I Know I've Been Converted / Evermae M. Paschal; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Heaven / Clarence E. Hatcher; Arranged by Kenneth Woods Jr.
    Faith and Grace Is All I Need / I. J. Johnson; Arranged by Tremerell Hunter
    Thank You, Jesus / Kenneth Morris
    Chicago, IL: Theodore R. Frye Publishers
  - Frye's Echoes of the Baptist Music Convention, No. 2, 1948; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 5)
    I'll Serve Jesus / Samuel E. Lewis; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    God's Amazing Grace / Roberta Martin; Arranged by J. Morris
    Only Believe / Paul Rader
    The Last Mile of the Way / W. E. Marks and Rev. Johnson Oatman
    Well, Let's Talk About Jesus / Henrietta Coleman; Arranged by Kenneth Woods Chorus
    In My Home Over There / H.J. Ford; Arranged by R. Martin
    Jesus Is The Name / Doris Akers; Arranged by Charles J. Levy
    The Unclouded Day / Rev. J.K. Alwood; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    My Soul Is Satisfied / Cleavant Derricks
    I'm Going To Tell The World Why Jesus Died / Samual A. Lewis; Arranged by Virginia Davis
    The Light Is My Guide / Lucille Henderson; Arranged by K. Morris
    He Delivered Me / Doris Akers; Arranged by Charles J. Levy
    He Will Remember Me / E.M.B.
    Tell Him All About It / Frances Johnson and Virginia Davis
    How Jesus Brought Me Out / Emma L. Jackson: Arranged by Jeanette Tall
    I'm Standing On The Highway / The Birmingham Blue Jay Jubilee Singers; Arranged by Viola Bates
    Now Lord / Sylvia Boddie; Jeanette Tall
    Jesus I Turn To Thee / Theodore R. Frye; Arranged by V. Bates
    He Is Our Savior / Dr. J.F. Jones; Arranged by G. T. S. Lucas and J. P. Powell, Jr.
    When I Get Home / Robert L. Glynn
    Glory, Glory Hallelujah; Arranged by Morris
    This Same Jesus / H.J. Ford
    Come, Ye Disconsolate / S. Webbe, Thomas Moore andThomas Hastings
    What Manner Of Man Is This / Deacon Roman Holmes; Arranged by Jeanette Tall
    What Jesus is to Me / Emma L. Jackson
    I Need Thee Ev'ry Hour / Robert Lowry; Arranged by Doris Akers
    Meeting Tonight On The Old Camp Ground; Arranged by Sylvia Boddie
    Jesus Put A Song In My Soul / H. J. Ford; Arranged by Martin
    He Suffered For You And Me / Virginia Davis
    I Must See Jesus for Myself - Someday / Kenneth Morris
    I'm On The Shining Pathway / John Hogarth Lozier
    I Am Happy In The Service Of The Lord / Fay Brown; Arranged by Virigina Davis
    I Will Run, Run, Run To Jesus / H.J. Ford; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    I'm Going To Walk The Milky White Way / Theodore R. Frye; Arranged by V. Bates
    How Far Am I From Canaan / Rev. W. Herbet Brewster; Arranged by K. Morris
  - Martin & Morris Gospel Star Songbook, No. 4, 1964; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 6)
    It's in My Heart / Arthur Slater; Arranged by J.G. Boersma
    It Was Jesus / Inez Andrews; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Sing A Song / Inez Andrews Gibbs; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    I'm Glad About It / Inez Andrews Gibbs; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    (Lord I Wonder) What Will Tomorrow Bring / Inez Andrews; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Peace Be Still / H.R. Palmer and Mary A. Baker
    All My Help / Rev. C. Robinson; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    In Times Like These / Ruth Caye Jones
    Balm In Gilead / Edward Boatner
    Waiting For My Child / S. Pugh; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    I'm Willing To Wait / Inez Andrews; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    I'm Not Tired Yet / Inez Andrews; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    You Don't Know Me Like The Lord Do / Inez Andrews; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Mary Don't You Weep; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Somewhere List'ning For My Name; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Show Me The Way / Inez Andrews; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Chicago, IL: Martin and Morris Music Inc
  - Martin & Morris Special Songs of the Pilgram Travelers, No. 16, 1950; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Just Over The Hill
    Jesus Is The Only One / Kenneth Morris
    In The Shelter Of The Rock / Anna B. Richardson; Arranged by Jeanette Tall and J. P. Powell Jr.
    Do You Know Him? / Mary Lou Parker
    Just Like Jesus Did / H. J. Ford
    I'm Going To Follow Jesus / Kenneth Morris
    Oh Lord, Stand By Me / Cleavant Derricks; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    Open Up The Pearly Gates / P.C. Smith and Kenneth Morris; Arranged by K. Morris
    In That Morning / Henrietta Makins
    I'm Going To Live with Jesus / Beulah Vaughns; Arranged by M. Brown
    Jesus The Way-Maker / Sammy Lewis; Arranged by Margarite Brown
    Thy Holy Will Be Done / Chalres Banks
    The Moment I Met Jesus / Kenneth Morris
    My Lord And I (On The Heavenly Road) / Lucie E. Camprell
    Jesus Met The Woman At The Well / Kenneth Morris and J. W. Alexander
    Come Home / Kenneth Morris
    I Come To Thee / Kenneth Morris
    Just Jesus / Milan G. Brown Jr.; Arranged by Kenneth Woods Jr.
    The Gospel Of Salvation Is Real / Ruth Hall; Arranged by Margarite Brown
    In The Name Of Jesus / Elder E. Howard Thurston; Arranged by Kenneth Woods, Jr.
    Do You Want To Go To Canaan Shore? / David Thomas; Arranged by Kenneth Woods, Jr.
    I Won't Have To Cross Jordan Alone / Charles E. Durham and Thomas Ramsey
    I'm Satisfied / Myrtle Jackson and Herbert Carson; Arranged by Jeanette Tall
    Now Lord / Sylvia Boddie; Arranged by Jeanette Tall
    I Never Knew Joy Before / Doris Akers; Arranged by Chalres J. Levy
    I Was there When The Spirit Came / Doris Akers; Arranged by K. Morris
    I'm Working For A Crown Over There / Ruth Hall; Arranged by Margarite Brown
    Shine On Me; Arranged by Virginia Davis and Emma Jackson Craig
    Something In My Heart / A. J. Twigg
    I'm Satisfied With Jesus / Anna B. Richardson; Arranged by Jeanette Tall
    Take It To The Lord / H. J. Ford
    Come Unto Me / A. B. Windom
    Touch Me, Lord Jesus / Lucie E. Campbell
  - The Three Stars Gospel Songbook, 1941; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 8)
    All That I Need is in Jesus / Homer Fuller; Arranged by K. Morris
    Hold On! / Arthur Atlas Peters; Arranged by Gilbert Allen
    Heavens Gates Are Standing Open for Me / Kenneth Morris and Elijah Becham
    If the Lord Wants Somebody, Send Me, I'll Go / Cornelia Lacy Parks; Arranged by Mary Elizabeth Lacy
    I Know My Prayer Is Heard Up There / Melva L. Williams; Arranged by K. Morris
    I've Seen Trials An Tribulations, 'Long This Way / Mary Haynes and Eugene Haynes; Arranged by L. M. Bowles
    I wouldn't take nothing for my journey as I go / Robert L. Smith
    I Find Joy in His Company Every Day / A. B. Windom
    I'm Standing on the Rock King Jesus / Goldie Cunningham and Kenneth Morris
    Journey Home / H. J. Ford
    Just the Same / Elder Homer Fuller; Arranged by K. Morris
    I Feel the Spirit / Kenneth Morris
    Nobody Knows and Nobody Cares / Kenneth Morris
    Go and Sin No More / Homer Fuller; Arranged by K. Morris
    The Land of Pure Delight / Emma Campbell; Arranged by Martin and Morris
    Jesus is Enough for Me / Kenneth Morris
    The Church at the End of Life's Road / Kenneth Morris
    Until the Lord Shall Come / Kenneth Morris
    Well, Well, Well, Don't Worry 'Bout Me / Famous Five Soul Stirrers; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    You Need Jesus on Your Journey / Necie G. Seaberry; Arranged by Kenneth Morris
    You Don't Have to Worry if Your Heart is Right / Kenneth Morris
    Chicago, IL: Martin and Morris Music Studio
  - Unidentified songbook (cover missing), pages 1, 22, 23, 1938; 1 song book (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Freedom Afterwhile / Theo. R. Frye, Lillian Bowles and W. O. Hoyle; Arranged by K. Morris
    Holy Spirit / E. Clifford Davis
    Something Within / L. E. Campbell
    General
    Dedicated to the memory of the late Rev. E.W.D. Isaac Sr. D.D.
  - "But This I Pray, Oh Lord Remember Me" by Myrtle Jackson, 1944; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Some stains, and autographed on cover in blue ink by Blondell Hill.
    Chicago, IL: The Martin Studio of Gospel Music
  - "Chorale from Finlandia" by Jean Sibelius, arranged by H. Alexander Matthews, 1934; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Philadelphia, PA: Oliver Ditson Company
  - "Does Jesus Care" by Kenneth Morris, 1943; 1 Score 3 copies (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Chicago, IL: Martin & Morris Music Studio
  - "God Be With You" by Tomas A. Dorsey and Artelia W. Hutchins, 1940; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Chicago, IL: Thomas A. Dorsey Music Publisher
  - "God Is Wonderful" by Virginia Marshall, 1964; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Top edge and title trimmed, folded with tears in margins.
    Waco, TX: Sacred Songs
  - "He Delivered Me" by Doris Akers, arranged by Charles J. Levy, 1948; 1 Score 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Los Angeles: Simmons and Akers Music Room
  - "Here Am I, Lord, Send Me" by Lillian M. Bowles, with words by W. O. Hoyle, 1937; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Chicago IL: Bowles Music House
  - "He Saved Me Too" by E. C. Deas, 1916; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "How Jesus Brought Me Out" by Emma L. Jackson, arranged by Jeanette Tall, 1943; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Image of Chicago gospel singer Beatrice Lux on cover.
    Chicago, IL: Jackson Studio of Gospel Music
  - "I Call Him Jesus, My Rock" by Virginia Davis, arranged by V. D. Lively, 1950; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "I'm Goin' To Bury Myself In My Jesus Arms" by Kenneth Morris, 1945; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Jesus" by Mary Lou Coleman Parker, arranged by Virginia Davis, 1948; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Mt. Vernon, IL: Parker's Music Studio
  - "Let Mount Zion Rejoice" by J. B. Herbert, 1923; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Dayton, OH: Lorenz Publishing Co.
  - "Lord I've Tried" by Rev. W. H. Brewster, arranged by Kenneth Morris, 1945; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Make Me a Blessing" by Geo. S. Schuler and "There Is a Fountain" by Lowell Mason, [1924]; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Photocopy from book, two songs on one page.
  - "Move on Up a Little Higher (Spiritual)" by Cordelia Monroe, arranged by Virginia Davis, 1948; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Norfolk, VA: The Monroe Music House
  - "My Testimony for Jesus" by Lucille Thompson, arranged by Kenneth Morris, 1945; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Now Lord" by Sylvia Boddie, arranged by Jeanette Tall, 1948; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Chicago, IL: Sylvia Boddie Music Studio
  - "O Blessed Jesus" and "We Adore Thee" by Palestrina, arranged by James Allan Dash, 1951; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Baltimore, MD: Baltimore Music Co.
  - "O Come All Ye Faithful" arranged by Carl Berger, 1940; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    New York, NY: G. Schirmer, Inc.
  - "Oh Lord, Stand By Me" by Cleavant Derricks, arranged by Kenneth Morris, 1948; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Only a Look" by Anna Shepherd, arranged by Virginia Davis, 1948; 1 Score 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Precious Memories" by Roberta Martin and Georgia Jones, 1939; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "The Shepherds Had an Angel" by Cecil E. Lapo, words by Christina Rossetti, 1947; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    New York, NY: Edwin H. Morris & Company
  - "Touch Me, Lord Jesus" by Lucie E. Campbell, 1941; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Memphis, TN: Lucie E. Campbell
  - "The Unclouded Day" arranged by Roberta Martin, 1943; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Faded image of Roberta Martin Singers on cover.
    Chicago, IL: Roberta Martin's Studio of Music
  - "Walk in Jerusalem" by E. M. Bartlett, 1938; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "When My Life Is Over" by Anna Thomas Chinn, 1943; 1 Score 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Image of Anna Thomas Chinn on cover.
    Chicago, IL: Theodore R. Frye
  - "Without Him" by Mylon R. LeFevre, 1963; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "You Can't Beat God Giving" by Doris Akers, 1957; 1 Score (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Los Angeles, CA: Manna Music, Inc.; distributed by Simmons and Akers
  - Song Texts, undated; 13 Songs 11 pages (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Blessed Quiteness
    Canaan
    Foot-Prints of Jesus
    Have You Been Tried
    He Will Remember Me
    Hide Me In thy Bosom
    Precious Memories
    I'll Tell It
    I'm Going To Walk
    Joy In My Soul
    Leave It There
    Oh What A Time
    On the Jericho Road
    Sing Joyous Praises to the Lord
- 2. Ephemera, 1950-1958; undated; 3 Folders